androidresult.com 2019-05-30

# Privacy - Android Result

Android Result is committed to preserving the privacy of all our users. Before you start using our website, please carefully read the following privacy policies in order to learn how to protect and use the information you provide us.

**Information that we collect**

In order to become a registered user of our website, we require you to provide us with some basic information such as your email id. We will not disclose your email id to other users. Your desired username is the only thing that other users would see. By providing us with your personal information, you allow us to store and process that information. Also, we might be collecting information regarding your interaction with our website and other users. We will store your IP address to solve server problems and provide assistance. We will use your information to perform statistical analysis in order to determine the interest and the use of different areas of the website.

**Users under 16**

If you are under 16, it is compulsory for you to obtain the approval of your legal guardian before submitting personal information to us such as your e-mail id.

**Security**

In order to safeguard the information that we have collected, we have employed different security measures on our website. These security measures include organizational and technical measures that are designed to safeguard your personal information from authorized access and accidental loss.

**Public forum**

We allow our user to interact with each other however, we do not allow users to use bad language while conversing with other users. Also, we are not to be held responsible for the personal information that a user discloses on a public forum. We recommend users not give personal information such as contact number or email id on a public forum.

**Changes in the Policy**

We reserve the right to change our policies at any time, however; the changes that we make in the future will be posted on the website. So, we recommend that you check the privacy policy page every now and then in order to remain updated regarding the current privacy policies.

**Third Party Advertisement**

Third party advertisement is allowed on our website and these companies might use information about your visit to our websites such as the areas of the website you visit the most and the ones you visit less in order to determine the kind of ad they would like to place on our website. This information does not include your personal information such as your email address.

**Contact the US**

If you want to ask a question regarding any of our privacy policy, you can always contact us.
